Yuri…
It was not as easy
as we anticipated getting this Novichok.
Custom inspector doubled his price.
Which means harbormaster doubled his.
Behind the shop.
The trunk of blue BMW.
Olek! Olek!
You're up.
I just woke up.
What?
When do you think the bump comes?
- Well, I googled a lot last night.
- Mmm.
I did not google that.
I hope soon.
I love a baby bump.
Okay, up.
- Okay.
- It's gonna be a busy one.
Go make coffee.
I hate to tell you this,
but Google says you can't drink coffee.
Just a sip.
Our baby can be
one IQ point shy of genius.
Okay.
Not in the Christmas spirit?
Historically? Never.
But this Christmas is an exception.
This Christmas
is a full-tank Merry Christmas.
It's a happy Christmas
like they have in England.
Why don't we say that here?
Happy Christmas.
♪ Have a holly jolly Christmas ♪
♪ It's the best time of the year… ♪
See? I love Christmas.
I don't love that
we're working Christmas Eve.
But you know, I love
what we're coming home to celebrate.
This is what we wanted
and we got what we wanted.
Right away.
It's okay to be nervous.
I'm not scared.
Just, you know, thought I'd be
further along by the time this happened.
You know, like, in life.
Have a plan, have a career, have a dog.
You want a dog?
You don't?
Hey, I like our life.
Me too.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
I'm with you. Thinking about our kid.
And I'm thinking about our dog.
Let's have a baby first.
Yeah, let's have a baby first.
I know what I want for Christmas.
I want you to seriously consider
applying to the police academy again.
Wait.
Good morning.
Getting closer, Walter.
Almost killed me that time.
Why the academy all of a sudden?
Because it was the last time
you were excited about your life.
You checked the mail so many times,
you knew the mailman by name.
I always knew Harry. We're like that.
It was like you could see a future
and you couldn't wait for it.
And the second that you didn't get in,
that guy checked out.
You miss him?
You miss him.
Well, they rejected me.
Once.
You applied once.
How many times did you ask me out?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You followed me to LA
when I got a job here.
And then you took a job at the same place
so we could have lunch together.
- That was three years ago.
- I like having lunch with you.
You asked me out.
Just, you know, saying.
Just do me a favor and think about it.
Thank you.
That's my favorite family today.
They're three hours early
for Flight 338 to Tahiti.
You always wanted to go to Tahiti.
I promised I'd take you someday.
Maybe tomorrow.
You know what looks amazing in a bikini?
A baby bump.
- I'll see you at lunch.
- Okay.
Tahiti tomorrow.
Yeah, Merry Christmas to you too.
Airports turn people into such dickheads.
- Here he is. Good morning, Keegan.
- Morning.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
This guy.
Your timing is perfect.
Good morning, Day Shift TSOs.
Good morning is a figure of speech
'cause no part of today
is gonna be good.
As if the holidays
weren't stressful enough,
you've all been chosen to spend
your Christmas Eve here with me
and 200,000 impatient travelers
about to come through your lines.
And they could come two hours early
like we tell 'em to, but they don't.
So they're late, they're anxious
and they're gonna
take all their shit out on you.
They will try to bait you into a fight.
Do not take the bait. So what is
going to be our mantra for the day?
Keep the line moving,
keep the people safe.
"Moving" and "safe." If we do that,
you, me and 200,000 passengers
will forget today ever happened.
Ah, Kopek, just in time…
to miss everything.
- Officer Williams?
- Yep. All right, listen up folks.
DHS has just alerted us
to fraudulent boarding passes
coming out of SeaTac yesterday.
Take a look at that.
You've all been issued
brand-new counterfeit pens.
I need you to use them. Okay?
And call me or any other LEO
for all inspections.
- What?
- Damn!
This whiney thing that you're doing?
My old ears can't even hear it.
All right, let's go, guys.
Stay alert. Stay vigilant.
Let's get through this
godforsaken holiday.
New $ANTO$ album
on SoundCloud and Patreon.
Ten tracks of fire
that'll make them cheeks clap.
Eddie, you're gross.
Don't act like you ain't about it.
My lyrics are body positive,
they sex positive,
and they open to anything except judgment.
Pek, you got support
for an emerging artist?
Okay. I have four whole dollars
on me, Eddie.
I'm giving you two.
Play track two
and your girl will have twins.
I text one person.
Well, good news travels fast.
- Hey.
- Yo.
How many people did you tell?
Literally every person that I saw
since you told me.
People need love in this world, man.
Let them be happy for you.
Hell, I'm happy for you.
Kids are a curse,
but they're also a blessing.
I thought you and Rochelle
were taking the boys to Murrieta.
We are. She's headed up this morning.
I'll meet them after my shift.
Listen up, everybody.
It is that time of year again.
Contraband Bingo is live. Yeah.
Five bucks per card.
No cash. No card. Edward.
Gummies, dildos, vibrators, knives,
bullets. Everything gets a square.
Not getting into the academy was a sign.
Maybe that's not where I should be.
I'm saying that I got here
two months after you
and I've got two promotions to your zero.
She's right. You're coasting over here.
And shit is about to get a lot harder.
Babies are chaos bots, bro.
They break things, stain shit.
There's a whole bunch
of liquid everywhere.
- I can do hard.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
She just wants you to show up.
Okay?
I believe in you. I'll see you out there.
Um, can I talk to you for a second?
Yeah, it's gonna have to be on the move.
I wrote a speech,
but it feels kind of stupid now.
Um, I've been thinking
about my career trajectory.
Your career trajectory?
All right. I think it's a flat line.
I got off to a slow start,
but I'd like to do better,
I'd like to do more.
Are you going to ask me for a bump?
Yeah.
Wow!
Ten minutes late to the meeting
and you're asking for a promotion.
You're growing
a real set of balls there, young man.
Let me see your speech.
It's on my phone, so…
Let me see it.
Yeah, no.
- Look. Nora's pregnant.
- Yeah, I heard.
So you decided to participate in life.
Great. Welcome to the shitshow.
I'm not giving you a promotion, okay?
I need guys that give me
more than bare minimum,
guys who want to be here.
- I want to be here.
- No, you don't.
Nice speech though.
And congrats on the kid.
You're right. I haven't shown initiative.
Uh…
And I'm… I came in late today,
like I sometimes do.
But I ranked top level
in threat assessment.
I've never had a complaint and I can
spot a fake better than the LEOs.
What?
I want to be here. I know I do
because I thought about quitting today.
But then I realized that'd be quitting
before I'd even tried, and that's on me.
I've been coasting, but I can do better.
Put me on a machine.
I'll show you I'm more than you think.
Leads are screening today.
Then give him my spot.
Yeah, that'll free up
a lead to work between D and E,
it'll keep us from bottlenecking.
Shh.
Hello, everyone.
Stay on departures for me, Chy.
Anyone parks longer than a minute,
you put a ticket on their window. Okay?
You got it.
See ya, bro.
Ethan,
big leagues now.
It's about damn time.
- What's this?
- Uh…
Here. Take this. Clorox pen.
You're on the front lines now.
Hey,
I gotta say, I'd be screwed
without you, Lionel.
Remove all outer layers
of clothing!
That's jackets, sweaters, everything!
Next, please.
All right, gentlemen,
the day shift is clocking in.
What's our status?
I'm on site.
Breaching now.
Okay, I've got eyes
on the target's family.
We have a problem.
Our target is not at the machine.
There's someone else at the scanner.
Let me see him.
Sending it to you now.
Stay calm. Pull his file.
Kopek.
Ethan Kopek. 30.
Born in New Brunswick, New Jersey.
Ran high school track.
He's been with the TSA for three years.
No commendations.
No promotions.
The family is about to leave.
I say we bag 'em
and force the target to resume his post.
That could attract attention.
Show me the alternates.
Lanes one and two
face the LAXPD,
and Ronald Dunn is former military.
Three years
and still entry-level. I know this guy.
The window's closing.
I need a call. Do I take the family?
He lives on Fifth and Rose.
You're five minutes away.
Okay, let's pivot.
Go to his place, fill in some blanks.
No matter what, this gets done today.
No belts, no liquids.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
This isn't mine.
Uh…
Remove your shoes
and place them in the bin.
I'll add it to the lost and found.
Over there.
Ethan, today is a day
that you're going to remember
for a very long time.
But if you handle it right,
you'll have a chance to forget it.
Hello?
One bag for one life.
Excuse me?
That's the deal.
That's what's going to happen.
Mmm. Yeah, nice try, Eddie.
I hope you rap better than you prank
or I'm out two bucks.
Eddie's in lane one,
driving his first Maybach.
Come on, lanes.
See how many bins I got over here…
Pay stubs, bills, family photos.
Anything we can use.
Just relax, okay?
This is how it goes, Ethan.
Soon an associate of mine
is gonna step into your line
with a boarding pass
for Northwind Flight 1850
non-stop to JFK.
You are gonna make sure
that his bag clears the machine.
This is a joke, right?
Is anything I just said funny?
No.
If it's any consolation,
you were not my first choice.
You're not where
you're supposed to be today,
but that is okay. To be honest,
it makes my day a little easier.
Okay. I'll play along.
- What's in the bag?
- Diamonds out of Papua New Guinea.
- Bullshit.
- Okay.
You answered too quickly.
Yeah, maybe because knowing
won't change anything
and I hope I don't have to execute
someone close to you to prove it.
Jason's house is right nearby,
a nice rental on Sixth Street.
Rochelle is home with the twins.
Why don't you ask me
if I know their names?
Who are you?
I'm just a traveler headed home
for the holidays, like everyone else.
Probably a lot like you.
If we met on the softball field,
I bet we'd be buddies.
We'd go out for beers after.
But we're meeting like this.
And I'm telling you how this goes.
Now, keep your voice down
and do exactly as I say.
- And you're watching me right now?
- Yes, I am.
And what am I doing?
You should put that down
before Sarkowski sees it.
I like this kid.
Okay. I found something.
I've got a pay stub, girlfriend maybe.
Sending it now.
Nora Parisi. Twenty-seven,
recently promoted to manager
of Northwind Operations.
Wait. I found something else.
Listen, asshole.
I work for
the Department of Homeland Security.
That's like the janitor at NASA
calling himself an astronaut.
You're a low-level TSO,
you're going nowhere,
and loving every minute of it.
He's putting a call through.
Hang up now or Nora dies.
What did you just say?
My people have
a Barrett M82 sniper rifle at her head.
Hang up the call…
- 911, what's your emergency?
- …Or we execute your girlfriend.
Your pregnant girlfriend
over at Northwind Operations.
Hello? Is anyone there?
I told you this is how it goes.
Hello?
Get up and lock it
in the lost and found.
Okay.
I said lock it.
The quicker you accept this,
Ethan, the safer you and Nora will be.
I accept it. Just be cool, okay?
Today won't be easy,
but it'll be simple.
When the plane departs at 5:40,
you and Nora are free to live your lives.
If the bag gets flagged, she dies.
If you talk to the police, she dies.
If anyone opens the bag...
Okay. I get it.
Good because I'm watching.
Now, you were a runner.
Pick a track, stay in your lane.
You've never made waves before, Ethan.
You're not going to start now.
One bag for one life.
All you have to do is nothing.
Congresswoman Grace Turner
still faces a significant challenge
in acquiring the votes in Congress
for her DTD Bill.
There's a vital conversation
we need to have about military spending
particularly its role in defending…
What the hell?
It's a topic that touches the core
of our International responsibilities…
- Sorry.
- …And national security.
Texting and driving.
Sorry.
What do you got, Detective?
Olek Vedenyapin and his nephew
Yuri Balakin. Olek was Bratva.
Yeah, he ran the port.
We've been trying to connect him to that
double homicide on Hawthorne last year.
Burn pattern suggests
some type of accelerant.
Nephew was shot dead before the fire.
Did you dig up a bullet yet?
Hydra-Shok. Bougie. Same COD as Olek?
We haven't found any other rounds.
ME will have to autopsy.
It's a cricket.
ATF bug. Standalone.
Bugs that broadcast can be easily detected
but this little guy
can record up to 72 hours.
Too bad it's cooked.
It probably recorded the murder.
I know somebody
who might be able to uncook it.
Everyone, the TSA would like to
personally congratulate you
for escaping the LA traffic.
To facilitate your getaway safely,
we're gonna play a game I like to call…
- Put it in a bin!
- Put it in a bin.
I'm not going through that machine
so you and your perv buddies
can take naked photos.
They always do this.
I'm late for my flight.
I have my student ID. Is that okay?
- Do you have a passport?
- No.
I will not bow to a repressive government
that wants to violate my human rights.
Keys, wallets, personal items.
Put it in a bin!
- Is this 'cause I'm Muslim?
- Is this 'cause I'm Black?
Is this 'cause I'm white?
You're putting on a show down here
so the cameras up there can profile us.
Do I look like a problem to you?
Your granny's cupcakes,
your mom's sweet potato pie.
Put it in the bin!
Bingo. Pay up.
Hey, you seem very tense.
I wonder why.
Well, when travelers see guys like you
get tense, they get tense.
And that's bad for me, which means
it's bad for Nora. Okay? So calm down.
You want me to be calm
with a gun pointed at my girlfriend.
Let's just try to put it
out of your mind. Okay?
Tell me about your holiday plans.
Yeah, okay.
I'm not asking, Ethan.
We don't have any, okay?
You have no holiday plans?
I sense maybe you're not
a fan of Christmas, right?
It's a holiday that makes
everyone feel they're not doing it right
no matter what they do.
They're never happy enough,
never rich enough, never enough enough.
Bah humbug.
To me, Christmas is all about family.
Really? The anonymous criminal
threatening my pregnant girlfriend's
- telling me the meaning of Christmas?
- That's a fair point.
Tell me where you met, you and Nora.
Post office.
Well, that's cute. I thought
your generation only met on apps.
Let me guess. She got a big job out west
and you didn't have anything else going
except her so you came along for the ride.
Now you got nothing else going on
in a whole new city.
Passengers bound for Chicago
on Northwind Flight 827
will be boarding soon at Gate 8.
How do your parents like her?
They approve?
They haven't spent a lot of time with her.
They live in Florida.
Hmm. Boy, that's nice.
Look…
I am not trying to piss you off,
but this isn't helping.
Nothing's going to take my mind off
the fact you're threatening my girlfriend.
Whatever you're trying to sneak
through security isn't going to work.
Naughty, naughty.
They got dogs and...
Let's cancel the text.
Reach down and cancel that text right now.
Attaboy. Now, stand up
and walk over to the drawer
and put the watch in there
next to your phone.
We're off to a real bad start here.
This won't work if I can't trust you.
Understand?
You can trust me.
You sure? 'Cause you've been
lying to me since we met.
Your parents do not live in Florida.
They moved back to the city six years ago
and your father used to work in private
security at the Freehold Raceway Mall
and your mother still teaches at PS 86.
Who the hell are you?
I'm the guy you listen to.
Now, I've given you two warnings
and the next time,
there's gonna be consequences.
Do you understand me?
Stop nodding and say it. "I understand."
I understand.
Good. My associate's on his way.
What's really in the bag?
It doesn't matter. The bag stays shut.
Okay? Say that.
The bag stays shut.
You know how many Targets
I had to go to to get these?
This is extortion, felony offense.
You'd do three years.
Well, you wanted a rush on your cricket
and I wanted peppermint Ho Hos.
They're delicious
and Shira won't buy Christmas flavors.
Mmm-hmm.
Oh, my gosh. That is so good.
I'm usually the only one here
on Christmas Eve. Get caught up.
- Shouldn't you be with family?
- Dinner's at 5:00.
Or 4:00, whatev…
What's up with the cricket?
You were right.
ATF's been surveilling this guy
for a while.
Mostly sells arms to Russians.
You think they're behind this?
Could be.
But something feels off.
Olek's been steady for years,
reliable for them.
Why would his Russian buddies
kill him now?
You got anything off the bug?
Not much. I took what I could restore,
isolated highs and lows.
Here's what I got.
Merry Christmas.
That's it.
You don't deserve Ho Hos.
It was in a fire.
This is a Christmas miracle.
Hallelujah.
You said you have a family?
No,
I said Christmas is about family.
- But I do have a son.
- Does he know what you do for a living?
He thinks I'm in insurance.
But that's not what
you really want to ask, is it?
Are you a terrorist?
No, Ethan, I'm not.
I consider myself
more of a freelance facilitator. Okay?
What does that mean?
Clients hire me
to facilitate a specific result.
It varies from job to job.
And what's the result you're after now?
Get a bag on a plane.
Right.
What about you?
You've been on autopilot
for a while now. Why don't you quit?
I will if you will.
No, I'm serious. A smart guy like you
had to have aspirations at some point.
What'd you have pinned up
on that vision board?
Well, you're the one who knows everything.
Why don't you tell me? Huh?
All right.
You're a son of a security guard,
you're observant.
How about… cop?
I'm right, aren't I?
Yeah, tell me what happened.
I didn't make the cut.
They kicked me out right before placement.
Oh. Why would they
go and do a thing like that?
- What'd you do?
- Next question.
A nerve hit. Okay.
You tell me when you're ready.
Was that it?
Did you ever reapply
or is that a touchy story too?
My dad wanted to be a cop.
Applied so many times
they flat out stopped responding.
You know what he does now?
Of course you do.
He drives an Uber.
Yeah.
So the world kicks him down,
you lie down next to him. Why is that?
Dreams have an expiration date.
I bet it's started to
eat at your relationship with Nora.
I bet she loves all the cynicism.
She has a different outlook.
I'm not saying chase your dreams.
That's not a very honest thing to say…
…but there is no need to hate
every minute of waking life.
Your generation is just so taken
with the concept of authenticity…
…that you will not take a bite
unless you know
it's the perfect hashtag real thing.
Real coffee, real pizza, real bagel.
The thing you kids haven't
come around to is that there's no real.
Fulfillment is a lie
that they use to sell paper towels.
Hey, now who's cynical?
No, I'm just experienced enough
to know life's disappointing,
and it's short and if you're smart,
you can steal
what happiness you can when you can.
Or just stay on autopilot
the rest of your life. Your call.
You know, the lucky ones find a job
that pays the most money…
…for the least amount of work.
And they spend the rest of their time
doing whatever makes them happy.
Like you.
You'd be surprised
how well I live.
Does it take a doctorate
to read a computer screen? Let's go.
- I need a LEO on four. Bag check.
- This is unreal.
It's called a book. You might read one
when you get your GED.
Buddy, relax. Let the guy work.
Sir, could I see
your boarding pass, please?
Mr. Herter, I need to conduct
a quick inspection.
If you prefer,
we can use a private room.
No, do it here.
I'm already late to board.
In that case,
I'll have a law enforcement officer
run your boarding pass while I search.
It'll save time.
I don't think this is necessary.
New fraud alert from SFO.
Yeah.
Okay.
You're all clear.
Probably just an imaging glitch.
You TSA guys are a joke.
- You know that, right?
- Thank you for your patience.
You can wait over there
for your boarding pass.
There's a story I once heard
about a tribe in the Serengeti.
Every summer when the game was sparse,
the tribe would depend on a single
apple tree for most of its food.
Then one day they learned
that the tree had been plucked bare.
The apples had been stolen
by one of their own.
"I'm sorry," the thief pled.
"I needed those apples
to feed my children."
The tribe forgave him and made do
until the tree bore fruit once more.
They returned, and lo and behold,
what'd they see?
The apples were gone again.
Pilfered by the same thief.
"I'm sorry," the thief begged.
"I needed those apples
to feed my children."
Even though the tribe was
without food yet again, they forgave him.
When the apples grew back,
the tribe's elders knew
the thief would return.
Excuse me.
So, when night fell,
they crept into the man's hut
and slit the throats
of all three children.
You want to know why, Ethan?
Because they learned that there can be
no lesson without consequence.
Somebody call a doctor!
- Call a paramedic!
- Get a doctor!
Officer down.
Back up! Everybody, back up!
Back up!
Hey, Nora.
Did you hear about the officer
at the TSO checkpoint?
- Yeah.
- Oh, my God.
Lionel. Sweet man.
I'm so sorry.
I've been trying to get a hold of Ethan.
He was with the guy.
- I don't know why he's not picking up.
- Go for it.
He was a friend of yours,
wasn't he?
It's a shame.
Family man like that
having a heart attack.
You killed him.
I don't know about that.
I gave you some simple rules.
You got cute. I'd say you killed him.
You feel like killing someone else?
Nora?
I told you.
I'm not some cartoon villain.
I'm just a regular guy like you
except with goals
and a clear plan to achieve them.
You, I see,
like to improvise.
"Active threat, not drugs, get Nora out,
find smuggler near bar arcade."
"Caucasian from New Jersey."
That's good. How'd you get all that?
You weren't worried about the dogs.
Whatever you're smuggling, it's not drugs.
Bagel, pizza references
and you call Manhattan "the city".
Hmm.
Only people from New York
or Jersey call it that.
Kept saying we're a lot alike.
I took a shot.
Plus, I've played Area 51
every day for two years.
I know that sound in my sleep.
You said I wasn't your first choice.
Supposed to be Jason, wasn't it?
Yep.
His twins are three.
You would have…
That would have been up to Jason.
But if I had to, without hesitation.
That's what you're dealing with.
I want you to think about that,
and I want you to think about Nora.
Then I want you to stop thinking.
Now, this is the way the world works.
There's people in control
and there's people that listen.
You listening?
Ethan, are you listening?
Yeah.
In a few minutes,
a guy with a red baseball cap
is gonna walk into your lane.
What do you have to do?
Nothing.
That's right.
Tell me there isn't something horrible
in that bag.
No.
Lionel.
It's messed up, man. You okay?
Yeah.
Nora called me, like, three times
trying to reach you. Call her back yet?
I will, thanks.
And thanks for covering for me.
I got it now.
It's all right, man.
Hey. Uh, you benching me?
No, putting you back on metal detectors.
Lionel's passing, this place is packed.
Today is not the day to experiment.
I'll give you another shot.
We'll talk about your future later.
But right now,
Jason's back on the machine
and that's final.
If you're not on that machine
by the time our man gets there,
you're in breach.
Then maybe I don't start with Nora.
Yeah, I don't care what you do to me.
Who said anything about you?
Your friend there
is coming off the machine.
You can decide
if it happens your way or mine.
Look, I…
My supervisor reassigned me.
What do you want me to do?
You're a smart kid, you'll figure it out.
Whatever you're doing, do it fast.
Not helping.
Hey, Ethan, I wanted to check on you.
What happened to Lionel,
it's tragic, so sad.
Yeah. I know.
I thought we could start
a GoFundMe for his family.
His wife and kids
I'm sure could use the help. Yeah?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm in.
You know, I think I heard
Samir talking about the same thing.
- You should hit him up. Join forces.
- Yeah.
Good idea.
What's up, man?
I think I left my phone
down the side there.
Do you see it? Down the bottom.
- There's nothing there.
- No?
Ah, I put it in the lost and found.
- You okay?
- Sorry. Yeah, just a bit out of it today.
That's not bad. Allow me.
Step forward please, sir.
All right, hold the line. Hold the line.
Raise your arms for me please.
Man, really?
Turn around for me please, sir.
This isn't mine.
- People's safety depends on you.
- I said it's not mine.
I don't care what problems you have.
Don't bring 'em here.
- It's not...
- Let's go. You're going home.
Ethan, you're back on four.
- Why? What's going on?
- Just do it.
Hey, you did good.
Go to hell.
I didn't say anything.
You know, it's pretty weird.
What?
How your buddy, who's our
designated driver every bar night,
gets himself fired
for drinking on the job.
I thought I met assholes before…
Okay, Ethan,
it's time to save Nora's life.
Red baseball cap,
three o'clock, by the bins.
That's our guy.
Nov… chuck.
Yeah. Get me Homeland.
Hey!
Ethan.
Thank you.
Let him go.
Proud of you.
Asset says the locals
put out a call to Homeland.
That's fine. This is why
we have options. Where's the kid?
Last call for Flight 1237…
There are 250 people on that flight.
- You gonna kill 250 people?
- Mmm-hmm.
I thought you said
you weren't a terrorist.
I'm not. Terrorists kill for religious
or political or social objectives.
Then why are you doing this?
I'm not the doer either, Ethan.
I'm just the one
that makes sure it gets done.
Then I get paid.
We're trained to identify explosives.
I've never seen anything like that.
Well, it's an A 234 nerve agent
called Novichok 7.
Causes instant cholinergic crisis,
followed by massive internal bleeding.
Russians love it.
Body breaks down, organ by organ,
until eventually you drown
in your own blood.
I'll take that phone, by the way.
Just put it right here on the counter.
Thank you.
There are kids on that flight.
Yeah. The people paying me
want to send a message.
One a busy world will have to hear.
What message? Who's paying you?
Ethan, the bigger the job is,
the fewer people there are
that can do it, okay?
And there are jobs happening all around
that most people can't see
and they all have casualties.
Fortunately, I'm the guy who can keep
those casualties to a minimum.
250 people is a minimum?
There are much larger numbers.
Why make me an accomplice?
Why not just check the bag?
Every checked bag is sorted through
automated CTX machines, you know that.
Our best odds are with carry-on.
We just needed a little fix
at the machine. Thank you.
Okay. It's through the machine.
You got what you wanted.
You can let us go.
Soon as that plane takes off.
Look, the hard part's already over.
A couple hours, you'll get your life back,
Nora's gonna be safe. You do love her?
Yeah, of course I love her.
Yeah? A lot of people say that.
I'm giving you
the opportunity to prove it.
Here's some gum. You want any?
Now, your shift's lunch break
is coming up. What are you gonna do?
I usually eat with Nora.
Great. I was hoping to get to know Nora.
Chew that gum, take her out to lunch.
I'll be listening. You guys brown-bag it?
No. Wait. I can't. I can't just sit
and act like everything's normal.
- It won't work...
- Ethan.
You break routine, you attract attention.
Almost done.
Agent John Alcott, DHS.
I'm looking for a Detective Cole.
- Down the hall on the left.
- Happy holidays.
You called Homeland
behind my back?
We're dealing with a potential
live threat. I made a judgment call.
Oh, by all means. Let's involve federal
agencies based on potential threats.
Elena, it's Christmas Eve. Go home.
Excuse me, since she already called,
I'm already here,
and I don't want to make the drive twice.
We take every threat seriously,
but your captain's right.
We cannot declare martial law
over a soft lead.
And how is this a soft lead?
An old-school Bratva underboss
maybe says the word Novichok
on a damaged ATF wiretap. I mean, come on.
Has there been
any chatter about an attack?
Always, but there's nothing credible.
There's no talk
about chemical weapons in Los Angeles.
Elena, you're reaching. Now, I'm going
home to enjoy dinner with my family.
- I suggest you do the same.
- Cap!
Hey, you know what?
Let me call my guy
at the Office of Bioweapons Affairs,
but I'm telling you,
he's gonna say the same thing.
EMS had a 911 call placed at 10:04
this morning from inside LAX.
Line is registered to a TSA officer,
guy named Ethan Kopek.
Told you.
I mean, Jason doesn't even
drink anymore. Like, ever.
Not since they had kids.
Rochelle would have told me
if he needed help.
Or I thought she would.
Maybe Lionel dying just…
- hit him hard.
- Oh. Mmm.
You know, we should actually go to Tahiti.
Never wait to celebrate, right?
Get more attentive, buddy.
You know, I wish we were there right now.
So, tell me.
What was your news?
I… It doesn't matter.
Of course it does.
Tell me.
Normal, Ethan. Keep it normal.
So I went to speak to Sarkowski.
About a promotion.
And he's going to give me a trial run.
Okay. And would that make you happy?
Well, I just thought, you know,
we're going to need things.
Doctors, car seats, cribs, clothes,
and, you know, those things cost money so…
Well, we can figure out money.
I only brought up the academy
because it was your dream.
It was what you always wanted.
Well, what if I don't know
what I want anymore?
- That is just sad.
- Well, then we'll figure it out… together.
Yeah.
Not the reaction
you were hoping for, huh, buddy?
I thought this was good news.
What would you tell our kid
if they got knocked down?
Oh, that's good.
You'd say, "Give it another shot."
Don't be afraid to fail.
That's a smart woman.
You should listen to her.
Tell her she's right. Go on.
- Tell her.
- Take a risk, Ethan.
- Stop telling me what to do.
Oopsie-daisy.
Hope you got her a good present.
Hey, I… Hey, I'm… I'm sorry.
That was too much.
You're just trying to help me.
Forget it. It's fine.
It's been a really hard day.
Yeah.
- We can just talk tonight, okay?
- Okay.
I, um… I gotta get back,
but call me end of shift.
Oh, you're gonna need
a big couch to sleep on tonight.
- Shut up.
- Well, I'm just saying.
Hi, beautiful girl.
- Merry Christmas.
Nora?
You're the best thing in my life.
You too.
Hey, you're back in the bed.
No one ran this down?
They did. Kopek's phone was off,
so they called LAXPD
and an Officer Lionel Williams
gave the all clear.
So it was logged as an error.
Officer Williams died
less than two hours ago. Heart attack.
- You don't buy it?
- And you do? Too many things.
- That's not a category of threat.
- What 30-year-old turns off his phone?
I need to talk to Kopek.
Okay, I'll go with you.
Thought it was a soft lead.
Spirit of Christmas.
Plus, I can call my guy on the way.
Rush order a tox screen
on Officer Williams.
Let's put an alert out,
conduct random passenger searches.
Kopek works the Northwind terminal.
Let's start there.
I'll get the ball rolling with airport PD.
They could use a head start given the
shitstorm we're about to drop on them.
You drive.
Texting and driving is how I kill people.
You're ordering a random sweep
of Terminal 7, middle of Christmas Eve,
the busiest travel day of the year,
and you're not gonna tell me why?
No, it's great.
People love missing their flights.
They come to the airport for the sushi.
Attention. To ensure
the safety of those traveling today,
the TSA will be performing
random bag checks.
If you are selected,
please accompany the officer.
Thank you for your cooperation,
and happy holidays.
- What's happening?
- How should I know?
We got a situation. I'm gonna
need you to shut down all the lines.
- All the lines?
- Yes. All of them.
All right, listen up.
All lines are officially on hold.
Everyone meet in the office. Right now.
Just one second.
Except you, Samir.
You deal with that. Good luck.
Y'all heard the call.
We're doing random sweeps.
- How many?
- I got a list of 50 passengers.
- Fifty?
- Yeah.
When we're done,
I'll have it sent to your MDTs, okay?
Work with the LEOs, find these people,
and bring them in for inspection, okay?
Gonna really slow things down.
- No shit.
- I didn't see an alert.
Didn't get an official alert.
I just got a heads-up from the LAPD.
So let's go over some protocols.
Lance, you and Samir are gonna be working
crowd control. Keep the lanes open.
The rest of us, we divide and conquer.
Okay, Ron? Need you to open up
the back rooms for inspection.
Do you have eyes on him?
No. The whole room is a blind spot.
Some of these passengers
won't be happy.
They give you shit,
you send them to me.
- Yep.
- This shit sounds serious.
- Is it weird I'm excited?
- Guys, don't get excited.
Just our buddies at the LAPD
- justifying their budget.
- This sucks.
Look, I know it sucks.
We can either waste our time
saying how much it sucks
or we get out and do our job
and find these people.
- So, let's go. Come on.
- All right.
Hey, uh, Ethan.
I know it's been
a particularly stressful day for you,
what with Jason and Lionel,
so appreciate you digging in.
I can see you want to be here.
I know what you did.
And I know why you did it.
Just didn't think
you'd be that kind of guy, bro.
Good luck with your promotion.
Jason, I can fix this.
Don't ever talk to me again.
You alone?
Yeah.
Good, get back to work.
Attention. To ensure
the safety of those traveling today,
the TSA will be performing
random bag checks.
The following passengers
are to report to a TSA officer.
Carrie Pierce. Cameron Figgs.
Mateo Flores. Alison Mallory.
Ethan, what did you do?
Nothing, I didn't move.
Why'd they pull my guy?
It's a lottery system.
Right in here.
You're lying. I don't know
how you did this, but this is you.
Sit right back down.
You leave that post, you're in breach.
There's nothing I can do.
Hey.
This is over.
Hey, Ethan...
He's on his way down. Change his mind.
Copy that.
Let's go for a ride.
Hey!
We gotta go.
What? Why?
- Rochelle texted me.
- No…
- She said you got Jason fired.
- I can explain but we have to move.
- So it's true?
- I had to!
I don't understand.
To get a promotion?
Why would you do that?
You speak one word,
and she dies.
You have three seconds to back away
or a 30-caliber round
will travel 3,000 feet per second
and paint the wall with her brain. Three…
Ethan, I need you to talk to me.
Two…
This isn't you.
Not one word.
So you're just walking away?
Departure gate for Flight 3678…
I was patient with you
because I thought I liked you.
Come here.
People tell you who they are
long before they open up their mouths.
You know what you told me?
That you're pathetic and you're asleep.
You're someone that's
so afraid to make a mistake,
you're willing to let
the whole world pass you by.
- That's how I knew you were my guy.
- I lied.
What's that?
I lied on the polygraph.
That's why I didn't get into the academy.
- Yeah? What'd you lie about?
- Well, I told him that…
Speak up.
Come here.
You think you can take control? Huh?
You haven't been in control since you were
on that shitty track team in high school.
So proud of the way
you can run fast in circles?
High school was as good
as your life would get,
so this will be a mercy kill.
Okay, okay, all right, all right.
Take it easy. Take it easy.
That's great.
Well, at least this is interesting.
What now?
First, you're gonna call your sniper
and when I confirm Nora's okay,
then I am walking you out to the police.
What if I do none of that
'cause the odds of you pulling that...
Let's do it your way.
- Okay. Slowly.
- Yep.
Then we're gonna do the phone.
All right? Let's take care of it.
Here we go.
What's the code?
The code?
You got ten minutes
before everybody in this airport dies.
- Shut it down.
- Payload will spread through all the ducts
in all the terminals in this airport
with 100% lethality...
I said shut it down!
I can't from here, buddy, okay?
Even if I wanted to, and I do want to
since I'm in this building.
I'll have to put my hands on it.
Okay, come on, you're not gonna
shoot me, Ethan. Think about it.
What happens after that?
I can disarm it in a minute-thirty,
I know what I'm doing. Do you?
Or maybe your Explosives Disposal Unit
can get there in time? I doubt it.
Would you rather kill 250 people
on a plane or 5,000 in an airport?
On Christmas Eve
it's probably closer to 10,000.
That's the thing with numbers.
They all get larger.
Okay, go.
No, you go. Go to the case
and I'll walk you through
how to turn off that timer, okay?
But don't talk to anybody.
Open up that mouth, I close mine.
- Why are you making me do it?
- 'Cause you're not in control, Ethan,
and you never will be.
Clock's ticking. So, go.
Take the gun. Maybe run.
And the other side, same thing?
No, sorry. That's the…
I made a mistake on the first side.
Three.
Is he alone?
- Doesn't seem to be working.
- I think my boss is in there with him.
That's fine.
Walk in and shoot the boss.
- What?
- Nothing fancy.
One in the head, two max.
It's a plastic gun.
Each shot generates heat.
If it melts, it'll explode in your hands.
No, I can't do that.
Really? You seemed ready
to kill me a minute ago.
- I can knock him out.
- No. We don't have time to experiment.
They're gonna die along with everyone else
in this airport if the bomb explodes.
You make the choice.
And look, Nora finally stopped crying.
- Back away.
- What are you doing?
Do it. Shoot him.
- I said back away from the case, please.
- All right. Backing away.
Don't know what this is about,
but I know you don't want to do this.
If you don't do this,
a lot of people are gonna die.
I have to.
About to be a father.
Do you want your kid
growing up with this in his life?
Put the gun down and we can talk.
He's done enough talking.
You're wasting time.
Shoot him now or everyone dies.
Please, don't make me do this.
- Shoot him.
- Who are you talking to?
God damn it, do it now!
Okay, and you're sure?
Okay. All right. Thanks, Marty.
It's my partner.
He just pulled the FAA manifest.
There's no high-value targets
leaving LAX today.
That's fine.
We'll just talk to the Kopek guy.
He knows something.
Oh, God.
I need a first aid kit.
No. Sounds like
your boss is past an ice pack.
Just get to the package
or everyone dies with him.
I didn't have a choice.
No, no, no! Please don't kill Jesse!
I don't know who that is.
My husband. He took him from my house
and he gave me that case.
You're not with them?
I'm like you.
Give me the codes.
Left 109, right 083.
- Oh, God.
- What is that?
Be quiet. Lock the door.
Okay, what do I do?
Do you see the two switches
on either side?
I want you to unlock those and then
lift it out of the case by the frame.
Okay, done.
There are two holes next to the timer.
Use them to turn
the circular plate clockwise,
then pull up.
Okay, now, disconnect the remote relay.
The button under the circular plate,
press it once to put it in manual mode.
Good, good.
Breathe if you haven't.
And then pull up on the handles
on the side of the cage slowly.
There are two clusters.
Grab the one on the right.
Pull it up slowly.
Once it's out,
you'll be able to see the reset button.
Hey! Why is this door locked?
Just a minute.
Kopek? Why are you in there?
There's a button that should be visible
between the brackets.
That'll reset the device.
- I can't reach it.
- Let me in.
What are you doing?
- Put it down.
- I won't let Jesse die!
Open the door.
Look at me. Look at me!
I can do it.
Please. Trust me.
- Kopek!
- Thirty seconds.
Kopek, open this door.
I'm not playing around.
Open the goddamn door right now.
- Yeah.
- You were right.
My three favorite words. What about?
Officer Williams.
The ME found a scratch on the back
of his hand with traces of aconite.
A cardiotoxin
that causes ventricular arrhythmia.
Heart attack was induced.
Homeland's in play now too, by the way.
They finally decided to check
the FAA passenger manifest
to see if any high-value targets
were flying through Los Angeles.
- Uh-huh.
- How about four of them?
The hell is wrong with you,
leaving me outside like that?
I was just… finishing up a bag check.
The room's all yours.
We have four Marines coming from Arifjan
to testify before Congress
on that Aleppo incident.
- Did we get their flight info?
- No. It's redacted.
But Homeland is sending
someone over with the raw data.
Okay. Give me his name. I'll bring him.
Agent John Alcott.
Okay.
That's great. Do me a favor.
Brief Conley. Tell him I'm en route to LAX
with Agent John Alcott right now.
But that doesn't make any sense.
What are you...
Elena?
You carried out a search
without a lead or a LEO present?
Sarkowski got called away
to ticketing.
Just trying to, you know,
speed things along.
Something's going on with you.
And I'm gonna figure out what it is.
I'm Ethan.
- Mateo.
- No, no.
Get acquainted later. You need to
dispose of that body and get moving.
Boarding time is in a half an hour.
- Everything all good?
- Yeah.
You know, the world
trying to make you feel like shit
because you go a whole five minutes
without checking your email
to enjoy a conversation.
- Who are you?
- Whoa.
Whoa, whoa.
John Alcott, okay? Homeland Security.
- I'm the guy who just backed your play.
- Mmm-mmm.
I offered to drive.
Agent John Alcott is on his way
to the station right now.
You intercepted my call to DHS.
Yeah, we've had a network
around your station for the last 72 hours.
Who's "we"?
And what do you want with the Novichok?
So what are you gonna do?
You're gonna shoot me
doing 70 down the highway?
We'll take him to sorting.
It's automated, no one will be there.
How'd you get involved?
I asked for a raise.
- Herschel… No.
- Are you all right?
No, not all right. Ping my phone.
Send somebody to ID the body.
- A body?
- Yeah.
Alcott… wasn't Alcott.
What the hell does that mean?
Elena? Elena?
Police.
- Oh, my God!
- Police.
- Are you okay? Okay.
- I'm police, I need the car.
I'm not playing, I need the car.
My man Ethan.
They spring you for Christmas?
No, not yet.
I gotta run this to sorting first.
I can take it. Let's get you home.
No, it's okay. I got it.
It's no problem. I could take this...
I said I got it.
Merry Christmas.
Mateo, can you, um…
Sorry, I'm eating.
Mateo, I'm speaking just to you now.
Cough if you understand.
Okay. I want you to listen,
but do not speak. Hold on.
Okay, put him through.
Mateo, it's me.
I'm okay.
They say you've done really well,
and that you're almost done.
They say there's one more thing
that you have to do.
Mateo! Listen to me. If you keep firing...
I'm… sorry…
We got here two hours early
like you told us to.
- TSA is completely disorganized.
- I know, sir.
Sir.
This is a restricted area.
Hey, miss. Miss!
Hey, you can't leave your car here. Hey!
…right here, we'll pull up
the outgoing flights to Jackson.
Hey, it's Nora. Please leave
me a message and I'll get back to you…
This new $anto$
is streaming on SoundCloud.
Forget Lil Nas X, forget Cardi B, baby.
It's the hottest thing on SoundCloud
right now, I promise.
LAPD!
Where's the security director?
Sarkowski? I think he's in ticketing.
Can I help you?
I need a line to LAX Security Tower
and I need to talk to Ethan Kopek.
Checkpoint Blue to STSO.
Do you have eyes on Kopek?
Sarkowski, do you copy?
Yeah, you looking for E?
He's on the way to sorting.
What is he doing down there?
The guy's been acting wiggly all day.
Shut this checkpoint down now
and put Tower on notice
for all Northwind flights.
You take me down there?
- Yeah, follow me.
- What's going on?
Ethan? Ethan!
Give me that case!
Can you hear me? Looks like I nicked you.
Hope you're all right. Give me
the goddamn case or Nora dies.
I don't wanna play hide-and-seek.
Ethan, I don't want any more nonsense.
Roll the case out.
All right. I'm done. Play it your way.
Listen up. Kill the girl.
Copy that.
Merry Christmas.
"Sniper in short-term. White van.
Ready Teddy. Get Nora to police."
"Terrorists Northwind 1850." This is real?
Hell if I know.
He's been acting all suss all day.
Talking to himself.
What's a "Ready Teddy"?
Eddie?
Move.
Head to the cops downstairs.
I got this.
Hey, man. What's up?
I got the deal for you.
Upgrade to business class select
right now...
What the hell is that doing here?
- What's the problem?
- That shouldn't be here.
Confirm with LAX Tower,
we have an active threat.
Pull all Northwind flights
and shut down Terminal 7.
This is Dunn. I need you to shut down
Terminal 7. We have an active threat.
Sir? TSA and LAPD confirmed
a live threat in Terminal 7.
Shut down 7 and all of Northwind.
But I'm not shutting down LAX
and grounding 300 planes on Christmas Eve
without a direct call from Homeland.
Baggage recovered,
but we lost our courier. Bring me a kit.
Hey! Help!
Don't move!
LAPD! Hands! Let's go!
Are you Kopek?
No, wait… No. Wait!
I know this looks bad, but you have to
let me go, I have to get to my girlfriend.
No. You are coming with me
and you're gonna tell me all about
the nerve gas. Now, where is it?
He still has it. Listen. Listen!
He's trying to take out Northwind 1850.
All passengers.
- I don't know if there's a target...
- You been shot?
I've been trying to stop them.
They threatened my girlfriend.
- There's someone after her.
- You're coming with me.
I'm sorry. He's getting on Northwind 1850.
White male. American. Fifties. Black hat,
black case with a red ribbon on it.
He's got ground support
and he's tapped into the cameras.
These guys are professionals!
Maybe see who could explain?
- I'm sorry.
- Where's Nora?
I saw her go downstairs.
Get out of the way!
Help!
- You okay?
- Yeah.
They hurt you?
You're Jesse?
My husband, Mateo Flores, is he…
He did everything he could to save you.
They said everything would be fine.
If he did what they wanted, they'd let him
fly back from DC tomorrow.
DC?
He's not supposed to be
on the New York flight?
They gave him two tickets.
Turner doesn't have the votes
because DTD is unconscionable.
You cannot underride
record military spending
while failing to account for the billions
that are handed out every year
to spectacularly profitable
private contractors.
To ensure global stability
and peace it is imperative…
Look who's on TV.
Well,
she's everywhere these days.
…to defend threatened democracies
protects our allies…
Yeah.
…and keeps conflict from our borders.
This strategy not only safeguards…
Have a safe flight.
…but it also serves as a deterrent
against potential aggressors.
By investing in the defense
of democracies, we create stronger…
LAXPD is aware
and sending you every hand on deck.
Everything coming into Terminal 7
is rerouted to Burbank or Long Beach.
But I have 60,000 passengers
in the rest of this airport.
And I gotta keep them moving.
Send me everything you got.
I'll let you know what we find.
Herschel?
Perfect timing. This just got super weird.
You can't surprise me today.
I'll try.
Fake Alcott is former Intelligence.
Any relationship with the Russians?
Not that I can find. He was discharged
under some heavily redacted circumstances,
then went freelance
for defense contractors.
Highest bidder types. They bid high.
Kopek said these guys are spread wide
and tapped in. Even painted a suspect.
Kopek? The guy who called us?
- You trust him?
- Keep looking for possible targets.
Start with Flight 1850,
and then widen the net.
Everybody with a flight today,
anybody with a profile.
Yeah, on it.
Attention. All flights
departing from Terminal 7 are delayed.
White male, fifties, black hat,
black case with a red ribbon.
Find him and do not let him board.
Oh, sweetie. Are you ready to fly?
Hello! He's so cute.
- How old is he?
- Eleven months old today.
- Have a safe flight, Congresswoman. Bye.
- Thank you.
I got an album coming out in two days.
You know what I'm saying?
It's on SoundCloud. Patreon.
We gotta find this bag.
I got this.
Nora Parisi, Airport Operations.
What's your seat number?
If the bag is scanned,
then I can find it anywhere.
Sorry.
Sir, I'm afraid that's too big to fit
as a carry-on. I can check it for you.
- No, I promise you I measured it myself.
- See, it's already been flagged.
I'll take it to cargo myself.
It'll be there when we land.
I promise. Would you like
to take anything out of it now?
No.
- Thank you.
- All right.
Ready? Five, five, two, six, eight,
four, four, zero, three, five.
I got it. It's on Trans Global 0610
to Washington, DC.
They boarded.
I'll call Tower and stop the flight.
No. Wait, wait. If we stop the flight,
he'll just trigger it on the ground.
It'll kill everyone anyway.
I diffused it once. I can do it again.
I know what to do.
There's an LAPD detective
trying to stop the bomb.
Find her, tell her
she has to let that plane take off.
- Hey.
-  Hey.
That Aleppo case, it was a dead end.
Marines say the confession scrapped
the need to testify. Anything?
Maybe. Found someone traveling
with a small security detail,
but in a different terminal.
Name is Grace Suarez.
Wait. Hang on. That's Grace Turner.
The Congresswoman.
Her office has her flying under
her maiden name.
That's why she wasn't flagged.
Ladies and gentlemen, this is the captain.
Merry Christmas and welcome aboard
Trans Global Air Flight 0610
with nonstop service to Washington, DC.
She has been the face of DTD,
a huge spend for threatened democracies
around the globe.
Weapons manufacturers are all over this
thing, but she doesn't have the votes.
Think the Russians want to take her out?
Kopek said these guys are American.
Fake Alcott, a hired gun
for defense contractors.
It's a set-up. Plane full of people,
Congresswoman, all killed
by Russian nerve toxin on Christmas Eve.
Everyone blames the Russians for killing
the one who stood up to them.
Congress would rally around her bill,
open up a firehose of funding.
Private contractors
get more than they ever dreamed.
All they had to do was kill one of their
own and everybody on board with her.
- What flight is she on?
- Trans Global 610.
Tower needs to ground that plane now.
Where's Trans Global 610 now?
Taxiing to the runway,
preparing for departure.
You need to stall it.
Keep it on the ground.
Is this your guy?
It's a delicate situation. We can't do
anything to spook anybody on board.
Tell them it's a mechanical issue,
a delay.
Why? What am I dealing with?
Are you with LAPD?
You can't ground 610.
And who are you?
Nora Parisi, Northwind Operations.
You just tried to arrest
my boyfriend Ethan Kopek.
You can't ground that plane.
Detective, we have 610 on the line.
Yeah. Tell them to hold on.
Trans Global 610,
you are not yet cleared for takeoff.
Please stand by for further instructions.
I know what's on it.
Tell your boyfriend to stay out of it.
We've got a trained killer
on board with a bomb.
And the moment he sees
anyone coming, he will set it off.
Ethan can disarm it without him knowing.
It's the only way.
So you expect me
to risk a plane full of people
because your boyfriend who decked me
says he can defuse a bomb mid-flight?
He did it before, he can do it again.
Detective, we have 610 holding.
What am I doing here?
It's the only way.
LA Tower,
what's the reason for the holdup?
Trans Global 0610,
we have a Code 4 on the ground.
We're trying to assess with local PD.
Detective?
Tower…
Allow 0610 to take off.
You sure?
You heard me.
Good news, folks.
We've received the all clear.
Flight attendants,
prepare for takeoff, please.
Ethan!
This stopped being funny
the last time I shot you.
Nice touch switching out the bags.
Put that down and step away from it.
I'm dead anyway
if I let you set this thing off.
Might as well shoot me again.
Okay.
Movement in cargo hold, checking.
It's over, pal.
It was over the minute I met you.
You don't know shit about me.
LA Tower, we have
two armed individuals aboard the aircraft.
We're declaring an emergency.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is the captain speaking.
For your safety, we are returning to LAX.
Flight attendants,
please prepare for landing.
Talk all you want while you can.
You're about to die
with everyone else on this plane.
I don't even have to shoot you again.
All I have to do…
is nothing.
You think bombs spoil?
Nice work.
Still wanna know
why I flunked that polygraph?
No, thanks. I'm gonna be busy
setting up my parachute and my bomb.
They asked if I ever saw a crime
that you didn't report.
Let me guess. Your dad, right?
Yeah.
Lifted a few bucks from the till?
You lied for sad old Dad, huh?
I was just trying to protect him.
I never was much of a liar.
Yeah? Well, you protected him
and then they threw you out
and you've been like him
ever since, right?
A loser, a waste, and asleep.
I guess I woke up.
Ethan!
Freeze!
Stay right there.
On your knees! On your knees!
No, wait! Don't shoot! I'm not the guy!
I'm not the… guy!
FD set up in five.
Plain sight.
Let's go!
- Set up a perimeter.
- Let him go.
- Set up triage over there!
- Intercept in 30 seconds.
Where's the Novichok?
Vacuum-sealed in a fridge.
And the guy?
Same fridge.
We've got a dispersed nerve agent.
Send in Hazmat,
get all these passengers out of here now.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Get him to a medic.
- No, ma'am.
- Ethan!
- No, we can't have you go in right now.
- Hey.
- Nobody's going any further.
- Let her through.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Set up a perimeter over there.
I knew you could do it.
Hazmat.
Watch your steps coming down, folks.
I love you.
Yeah, I'm sorry I hit you.
Mmm-hmm. You got good instincts, Kopek.
Call me when you get that stitched up.
Yeah.
- Hey.
Tahiti today?
About time.
Ooh, so cute. But maybe we can do this
on the other side.
- Yes, sir.
- This line is ridiculous.
How long does it take you
to wave a wand over an old lady?
Hey!
She's just doing her job.
Happy Christmas.
All right. Let's go.
Yo, left foot, right foot,
left foot, right foot…
Oh…